pokemonradargo.com 2017-05-15

# Privacy Policy | Poke Radar for Pokemon GO - Maps, Finder, Search, Locations

Titanic Labs, Inc. respects the privacy of our users and has developed this Privacy Policy to demonstrate its commitment to protecting the end user's (hereafter, "you" or "your") privacy. This Privacy Policy is intended to describe for you, as an individual who is a user of the Poke Radar application, the Poke Radar website, and all websites and URL's controlled or operated by Titanic Labs, Inc. which link to this policy, unless otherwise specified.

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using our website or services or transacting business with us. By using our website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us.

### Information we collect about you

 _In General_

. We may collect personal information that can identify you such as your name and email address and other information that does not identify you. When you provide personal information through our website, the information may be sent to servers located in the United States and other countries around the world.

  *  **Information you provide.** We may collect and store any personal information you enter on our website or provide to us in some other manner. This includes identifying information, such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card information, and other personally identifiable information.
  *  **Information from other sources.** We may also periodically obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from business partners, vendors and other third parties. Examples of information that we may receive include: purchase history, and additional demographic information.

 _Use of cookies and other technologies to collect information._ We use various technologies to collect information from your computer and about your activities on our site.

  *  **Information collected automatically.** We automatically collect information from your browser or application when you visit our website or use our services. This information includes your IP address, your browser type and language, access times, location, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us (see "Cookies" below), and the referring website address.
  *  **Cookies.** When you visit our website, we may assign your computer one or more cookies, to facilitate access to our site and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our site, such as the web pages you visit, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on our site. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the interactive features offered on our website.
  *  **Other Technologies.** We may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use of our site. We also may include web beacons in promotional or other e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer our website visitors to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming or other activities.
  *  **Information collected by third-parties.** We may allow third-parties to display advertisements on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies or web beacons, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness.

  *  **Password**  
Use of portions of the Site requires you to enter your trainer name or password. You agree that you will be responsible for maintaining your password as confidential and for any activity that occurs on your Account as a result of you sharing your password with another or failing to protect it. Titanic Labs, Inc. is not responsible for any loss or damage arising from your failure to maintain the confidentiality of your password.
  *  **User-Submitted Information**  
Titanic Labs, Inc. reserves the right to retain any and all information submitted by Users through use of the Site, including but not limited to reviews, public profile information, information submitted to surveys (created by us or any other third party), personal messages sent through the Site, and posts to message boards or forums. We may supplement Personal Information you provide us with additional information purchased from third parties for marketing purposes.

### How we use the information we collect

 _In general._

We may use information that we collect about you to:

  * deliver the products and services that you have requested;
  * manage your account and provide you with customer support;
  * perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others;
  * communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices or send newsletters about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or other third parties;
  * communicate with you with regard to partially completed service requests;
  * develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our site and other sites;
  * verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and sweepstakes;
  * enforce our terms and conditions;
  * publicly-display comments, ratings and reviews and other content provided by you;
  * manage our business; and
  * perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

### Social Networking

We maintain presence on several social networking, such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, and we also may incorporate some third party social networking features onto our Site or utilize third-party provided platforms to publish or manage the Site or portions thereof. Through these platforms and features, we receive some Personal Information and some Site usage information about you, and this Privacy Policy applies to that information as well. In addition, some providers of third party social networking or blogging platforms we utilize (such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest) have their own privacy policies which explain how the third parties that provide them may collect, use and protect your information (e.g., if you establish an account with such platform providers directly).

### With whom we share your information

We want you to understand when and with whom we may share personal or other information we have collected about you or your activities on our web site or while using our services.

 _Personal information._

We do not share your personal information with others except as indicated below or when we inform you and give you an opportunity to opt out of having your personal information shared. We may share personal information with:

  *  **Marketing Affiliates:** When you are referred to us via a third party marketing affiliate, we may share your email address, and other information that you provide, to such marketing affiliate.
  *  **Business partners:** When you make purchases, reservations or engage in promotions offered through our website or our services, we may share personal information with the businesses with which we partner to offer you those products, services, promotions, contests and/or sweepstakes. When you elect to engage in a particular offer or program, you authorize us to provide your email address and other information to that merchant.
  *  **Direct mail partners.** From time to time we may share our postal mailing list with selected providers of goods and services that may be of interest to you.
  *  **Other Situations.** We also may disclose your information:
    * In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.
    * When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce our website terms and conditions or other agreements or policies.
    * In connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

Any third parties to whom we may disclose personal information may have their own privacy policies which describe how they use and disclose personal information. Those policies will govern use, handling and disclosure of your personal information once we have shared it with those third parties as described in this Privacy Policy. If you want to learn more about their privacy practices, we encourage you to visit the websites of those third parties. These entities or their servers may be located either inside or outside the United States.

 _Aggregated and non-personal information._

We may share aggregated and non-personal information we collect under any of the above circumstances. We may also share it with third parties to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our websites and on websites of third parties. We may combine non-personal information we collect with additional non-personal information collected from other sources. We also may share aggregated information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors to our website and the most popular features or locations. This information does not contain any personal information and may be used to develop website content and services that we hope you and other users will find of interest and to target content and advertising.

### How you can access your information

If you have an account with us, you have the ability to review and update your personal information online by emailing pokegoradar@gmail.com.

You can also choose to have your account disabled by contacting customer support. After you deactivate your account, you will not be able to sign in to our website or access any of your personal information. However, you can open a new account at any time. If you deactivate your account, we may still retain certain information associated with your account for analytical purposes and recordkeeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, enforce our terms and conditions, take actions we deem necessary to protect the integrity of our web site or our users, or take other actions otherwise permitted by law. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties' policies.

### Your choices about collection and use of your information

  * At any time a consumer user can choose to no longer receive commercial or promotional emails or newsletters from us by following the unsubscribe directions in such messages. It may take up to 10 days for us to process an opt-out request. We may send you other types of transactional and relationship e-mail communications, such as service announcements, administrative notices, and surveys, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.
  * If you prefer not to have us share your postal mailing information with these selected providers of goods and services that may be of interest to you, you can notify us at any time by emailing us at pokegoradar@gmail.com.
  * #### Blogs, bulletin boards, reviews and chat rooms

We may provide areas on our websites where you can post information about yourself and others and communicate with others, as well as post reviews of products, establishments, contractors, and the like, or upload content (e.g. pictures, videos, audio files, etc.). In addition, such postings may appear on other websites or when searches are executed on the subject of your posting. Also, whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on publicly-viewable web pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited messages. We cannot control who reads your posting or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal information. Once you have posted information, you may not be able to edit or delete such information.

#### Children's privacy

Our website is a general audience site, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from or target children under the age of 13.

### Visiting our websites from outside the United States

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on our website from residents of the United States. If you are visiting our website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this privacy policy.

### No Rights of Third Parties

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the website.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will notify you by posting the updated policy on our website, with a link denoting that the policy has been updated. We recommend that you check our website from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies

### How to contact us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information-handling practices please contact us by e-mail as follows:

pokegoradar@gmail.com.

### Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of California, in addition to the rights set forth above, you have the right to request information from us regarding the manner in which we share certain categories of personal information with third parties. California law gives you the right to send us a request at a designated address to receive the following information:

  1. the categories of information we disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year
  2. the names and addresses of the third parties that received that information; and
  3. if the nature of the third party's business cannot be determined from their name, examples of the products or services marketed.

We may provide this information in a standardized format that is not specific to you. The designated email address for these requests is pokegoradar@gmail.com.
